{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"8.04/90.6",
			"answer":"8.04/90.6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"75.2/8",
			"answer":"75.2/8",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.28/2",
			"answer":"0.28/2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"248/2",
			"answer":"248/2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"55.5/5",
			"answer":"55.5/5",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2.76/0.006",
			"answer":"2.76/0.006",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"51.1/7",
			"answer":"51.1/7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.312/0.4",
			"answer":"0.312/0.4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"6.33/0.3",
			"answer":"6.33/0.3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"1.11/0.0003",
			"answer":"1.11/0.0003",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}


	]
}